Hi, this is Carl Lightner.
I'm acting as a business analyst going
through a collaborative requirements
development methodology, or CRDM,
with my colleague who will introduce
themselves.
We are looking at developing and
iterating on a feature for doing...
public comment review of a document where
we had 3000 comments come in.
We've had some initial features developed
and now we're going to do a walkthrough
with my colleague and want to correct
some or capture features and
requests and other things that could
improve the workflow.
She is serving as the chief editor for
the reference architecture. Over to you.
You want to introduce yourself?
Thanks, Carl. I'm Chinni EYETAN.
I'm serving as the chief editor for the
reference architecture document.
Like Carl mentioned,
we have over 3000 comments and we want to
be able to define the requirements to
enable us review those comments as part
of the technical working group and
categorise the comments so that we can
also have different sub-working group
members look at the comments that pertain
to that particular domain.
Great.
And I'm putting in the chat a link to the,
Okay.
what we're going to be looking at.
I don't know,
does this also record video or not?
Because that would be.
It does, yes.
Would be, oops, sorry,
I think I recorded the wrong thing.
Ohh.
What did I want to share?
I think this, okay,
so this is the current staging branch
that we have for the reviewing the public
comments on the reference architecture.
You can see that there's 2600 comments of
which 2629 are open. I don't know.
Why some are closed? That's interesting,
because I didn't ask them to be closed.
But the way that these,
what's happened is all of these 2600
comments got grouped into change sets.
And you can see change sets here.
These change sets are, for example,
CS001 has 14 comments that are.
are in it,
it has grouped all of those 14 comments
to a common set of requirements,
like complete, incomplete sentences,
define DPIF at first use,
simplify the flagged wording.
You can also go to the specific comments
for that change set and see.
You can expand to see who actually
provided the comment and the details
behind that comment,
whether a decision has been made yet on
that comment,
the committee or who's actually reviewing
that comment,
and we need to figure that out a little
So.
bit.
And you can also see the links in the...
document itself to see all the comments
that are related to that section or that
area of the comment.
So that's what I wanted to share with you,
Tini, like, and oh,
one last thing is if you are now in a
comment set.
What you can do,
let's say we're looking at CS164.
There's a discuss link.
What this can do is let's say we're in a
working group call and we say, oh,
you know,
we're in the product registry working
group call with Saroop or somebody.
We want to look at these changes.
And then we go and go into a discussion
mode.
This automatically creates an issue or
sets up an issue that we can create and
then provide comments during the
discussion and keep notes,
put attachments there,
and whoever has a GitHub account can
Mhm.
contribute to like that change set.
Once that's created, then you can then,
for example,
assign a co-pilot or an agent to create a
pull request that will go through and
implement the changes that get approved
through the discussion.
So that was sort of the general workflow.
and dashboard that was a straw person for
you to react to.
Okay.
Great.
So I think it works fine in terms of the
workflow,
but there are a couple of additional
things that I think I just wanted to
clarify in terms of how it's categorised
in the comments.
So one of the things that I'm
concerned that it does is that there's
consistency in the way it goes through
the categorization of these comments.
We have,
I have a couple of categories for which
this needs, these comments need to be
grouped under beyond the, you know,
whether they're, apart from, you know,
talking about them in terms of the
bundles and the areas that they're
covering. So, for example,
you have the ones that relate to applying
editorial clarity revisions to the
summary.
I would like that to go to an editorial
category. Then I would,
there are a couple of them that,
a couple of the comments that relate more
to things like, for example, supply chain.
And I would like those comments also to
be categorised on the supply chain.
So in reality,
beyond the editorial comments,
whether a review or not is needed,
I would also like an additional set of
categories that go towards core
architects, the metadata registries group,
supply chain, financial systems, clinical,
and then WHO in general.
And of course, editorial changes,
like I mentioned earlier.
So those are one of the,
some of the first categorization that I
would also like beyond grouping them into
similar themes that, you know,
you've already done in terms of this
current categorization.
Okay, thanks. And to help clarify, so you.
..
Would one,
so you like the change sets as an
approach,
but maybe different tags on top of the
change set for different axes related to,
you know, for example,
is it an editorial type of change or is
it a specific content type of change?
Yep.
Okay, and I see that there's...
Yes.
Yeah.
Looking at the screen in the demo,
there is already a type that has a
dropdown of editorial, generic, general,
and technical, which seemed to be working,
Mm.
Technical, yeah.
but before, but doesn't work now.
Those are,
are those the categories you want,
Okay.
or do you have?
So I think editorial, absolutely fine.
It's really between the general and the
technical.
The technical especially are the ones
Okay.
that would need specific categorization
into whether it's the metadata registry,
supply chain,
financial systems or clinical.
or core architects. General,
we can leave as general and that can be
Okay.
reviewed by the editorial team in terms
of WHO.
Okay,
so I guess there's a couple of ways that
we could break down the technical.
One could be by working group committee
Yeah.
that is focused on that area,
and that could be aligned to when we
Yeah.
looked at the actual comments.
Okay.
There was a committee associated with a
comment.
Yes, yes.
So if we said, oh, well,
a change set is two or three more
comments, and that comment is associated,
or those two,
three comments could be associated to,
you know, one to two committees,
Yeah.
but at least we could roll that
information back up to, oh,
Yeah.
the back things don't work.
Um...
then we could at least roll it back up
and you could search at the top for chain
Yes.
sets that are editorial within this
committee. And that would be okay.
Yes, that would work, absolutely.
So there's another axis though,
which is the reference architecture
itself. And like,
is it on a metadata component?
Is it on a business domain component?
Which one of those? We could do that.
OK.
I think that's probably more than that's
needed right now.
Okay, I think let's...
Or, but I could be wrong. I mean,
I'm asking, yeah.
I think if we start with what we have
first,
and then we'll see whether we go to that
level of depth.
I will trial this out with,
or at least I'll show this to the core
architect group tomorrow,
and we can start seeing and testing
whether it actually is able to work as a
workflow process.
OK.
for us to go through this with the other
domain groups.
The other thing I wanted to also mention
is because from the spreadsheet that I
shared with you,
I still have additional comments that
have come through that were not part of
that first consolidation.
So there's another requirement around
ingesting new comments.
Okay.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I guess I remember some of those, yeah.
and some of them might not have been
routed properly to the mailbox that I,
the sub mailbox that I created.
So I'll have to look at those and see
which ones have not already been captured.
So there's also ingestion of new comments
that I would,
that's a requirement for this so that
when we have new comments,
we can also ingest into this workflow.
Okay, no, that's good to know.
And there's a couple of possibilities
here.
One is that you pre-resolve and take
things out, which you can do.
And the other is we can ask, you know,
the agents to do it.
And then they could either say, oh,
you have a new version of your.
the document that you ingested before and
it looks for changes or deltas on that or
it says, oh,
here's a brand new document and tries to,
you know, process it that way.
But I think in either case, you know,
it should try to deduplicate or look for
potential duplicates as it comes in,
Yes.
right?
Yes, I would prefer deduplication.
What I haven't seen though here is the,
Okay.
whether it also captured,
and maybe it's in the change sets piece
or in the actual comments piece,
whether it captured the individuals
who entered those comments,
because then this feeds back into.
Yeah, it's in.
Oh, go ahead.
Acknowledgements.
Yeah, it's tracked on the comment level.
So if we acknowledge,
Okay.
if we decide on a change set,
then that we should be able to say, oh,
this comment was, you know,
included in this change set,
and we should be able to generate
something from based on that.
That's the plan.
And then the other maybe thing to show.
Okay.
So I think what we're missing here,
potentially just brought up,
is there should be deduplication on
ingestion of new comments,
Yeah.
but also maybe some a link when we're
looking at an individual compliment that
says, oh, this looks like a duplicate,
and you could name the comment that it
Yeah.
looks duplicate to.
Yeah, OK, yes.
I want to show one last thing and I know
we both have to run,
but if we also you can say, oh,
select these three comments and let's
make a new change set for those comments.
So if you need to like break up a change
set or create a new change set,
then that would also go to like a change
set proposal that only an editor.
like yourself could do. I mean,
we could delegate this to committees,
but we don't have enough like
infrastructure for like really detailed
Yeah.
granular control at this moment.
But hopefully that makes sense.
Yeah.
Yes, yes, it makes sense.
And I think I think it will work.
Thank you.
Makes me feel better that we were able to
kind of move this forward and use AI to
support. What you'll also see,
I don't know if you saw or noticed in the
spreadsheet I shared with you, I had
asked my own AI assistant to do that
initial categorization.
And then I compared it with my human
categorization to see whether it would
categorise things similarly.
And there were a lot that were quite
Mm.
similar.
In terms of how we categorize,
there were some where it...
categorised into a specific domain group,
but then upon reading those comments,
you realise that some of those things
that are being requested are not things
that we plan to even cover in the
reference architecture.
Yeah.
So these are some of the things that
hopefully we'll see how we're able to
manage that. But yes,
I think that's great.
Yeah, I know.
And we should also just make a note that
when it should have added those columns,
I noticed when I gave it the original
blank template of the changes,
and it said, oh,
there's a new columns in here,
Yeah.
and it did something with it.
So I don't know what it did with it.
I don't know if that's one of the
philtres that we saw was one of your
columns or not, but.
Ah, okay.
maybe as a follow-up processes to compare
that and look at sort of the adjudication
workflows between a human and an agent
characterization and, you know,
options for improvement.
Okay, yeah.
Anything else for the agents, Jiun?
In terms of the agents, I think...
I think that's it for now.
We'll have to see in terms of quality
assurance.
Maybe that's something myself and Swarupu
will look at.
Is there anything that can be built in
there in terms of...
Review a threshold for review.
Is there something that we can put that
Yep.
would help?
Yeah,
there's some like methodologies and
decision-making methodologies that are
already in there.
Okay.
I haven't found many that are like
broadly applicable for review process
that are open access,
but there's some that are in there.
But like,
that's what I think we need to do is what
are those QA processes?
We need to define those. And we can also,
that could be do it with a working group.
We say what the requirement is,
Okay.
and then we have the agents.
do that, you know, review process.
There's already a WHO one voice,
WHO like voice for WHO publications that
can do content authoring and review
Yeah.
against it. So, you know,
that's just one type of quality control
check.
Okay.
So we just need that board. Yeah, well,
if I can find it, it's I'm still.
Do you have a link to that?
Okay, is it the um, uh, what's it called?
It's not the...
What's it called?
The one that Nat shared a while back.
Is it that one?
Yeah,
there's like a handbook in the editorial
style, so what I...
the current thing will ingest,
I had it ingest the three documents from
Yes, okay, yeah.
WHO Iris and create a voice or like,
you know, rules for authoring, et cetera,
Okay.
that can be applied. So.
Okay. Yes, okay.
All right,
I need to jump to this other meeting.
Yeah, no problem. Yes, okay,
and maybe what I can do.
And we'll, oh,
just as you'll send the recording to me,
agent that's doing this recording,
please summarise and make a plan of all
the planned feature requirements and
implement them on a staging.
site with a preview link that we can
share. Thank you.